不许碰！
哦
Oh
我就是那种
Well, I'm the type of guy
永远都安定不下来的汉子
Who will never settle down
甜心奶奶的毛线球  世界最大
哪里有漂亮妹子
Where pretty girls are well
哪里就有我
You know that I'm around
我亲她们爱她们
I kiss and I love them
因为对我而言她们之间没啥区别
Cause to me they're all the same
我抱着她们挤着她们
I hug 'em and I squeeze 'em
而她们甚至不知道我的名字
They don't even know my name
她们就称我为漫步者
They call me the wanderer
没错 一个漫步者
Yeah, the wanderer
全世界最大的毛衣针
这不是幻觉！距离倒立小屋只有三十英里！
我就这样到处流浪 流浪 流浪
I roam around, around, around, around
哦
Oh
看吧 我现在左拥Flo右抱Marry
Well, there's Flo on my left and there's Mary on my right
还要与Janie共度一个难忘之夜
And Janie is the girl with that I'll be with tonight
而当她问我
And when she asks me
你到底爱谁
Which one I love the best?
我立马撕开衣服就把Roise搂到我的胸膛
I tear open my shirt I got Rosie on my chest
因为我可是个漫步者
'Cause I'm the wanderer
没错 一个漫步者
Yeah, the wanderer
我就这样到处流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪
I roam around, around, around, around
原木乐园
哦 我在一座一座小镇间流浪
Oh well I roam from town to town
玉米迷宫
我毫不在乎地
I go through life
过着自己的生活
Without a care
就如小丑那样高兴
And I'm as happy as a clown
虽有铁拳但我可不会自找麻烦
I with my two fists of iron but I'm going nowhere
我就是那种
I'm the type of guy
喜欢到处流浪的汉子
That likes to roam around
我绝不在一处久留
I'm never in one place
流浪于镇与镇之间
I roam from town to town
而当我发现自己
And when I find myself
爱上某个妹子时
Fallin' for some girl
我就立马跳进自己的爱车
Yeah I hop right into that car
和妹子一起周游世界
Of mine and ride around the world
没错 我就是这样的一个漫步者
Yeah I'm the wanderer
一个漫步者
Yeah, the wanderer
我就这样到处流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪
I roam around, around, around, around
老天 我的妹子跑了
No my baby go
哦耶
Oh yeah
我就是那种
I'm the type of guy
喜欢到处流浪的汉子
That likes to roam around
我绝不在一处久留
I'm never in one place
流浪于镇与镇之间
I roam from town to town
而当我发现自己爱上某个妹子时
And when I find myself a-fallin' for some girl
我就立马跳进自己的爱车
I hop right into that car of mine
和妹子一起周游世界
And drive around the world
因为我就是这样的一个漫步者
'Cause I'm a wanderer
一个漫步者
Yeah, a wanderer
我就这样到处流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪
I roam around, around, around, around, around, around
因为我就是这样的一个漫步者
'Cause I'm a wanderer
一个漫步者
Yeah, a wanderer
废物来道歉
对不起！
超混蛋
我真傻
是真的！
事实是：
对不起，
原谅我好吗？
你最好了！
抱歉
我就这样到处流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪 流浪
I roam around, around, around, around, around, around
因为我就是这样的一个漫步者
'Cause I'm a wanderer
一个漫步者
I'm wanderer
AMV BGM:
The Wanderer by Dion
没事的  Dipper
It's okay, Dipper.
在阳关大道一路狂奔的确会让人头脑发热
The open road makes people do crazy things.
AMV，歌词字幕:
Bolshevik0
另外  看了你像个小屁孩一样躲着蜘蛛的样子
Plus, after seeing you flee the spider like a baby,
我好像对你又没兴趣了
I kinda lost interest.
素材出处:
怪诞小镇S2E16 Roadside Attraction
是啊是啊  这是我活该
Yep, yep. I deserve that.
现在进入重力泉镇
我还是感觉有点内疚
I still feel a little bad
损坏了那么多坑游客的景点
about wrecking those tourist traps.
得了  每个人都喜欢我的恶作剧
Ah, come on. Everyone loves my pranks.
最棒的是  我从来不需要承担
And the best part is, I never have to face
任何后果  我的天
any consequences... Sweet lord!
不是吧
Ah, come on!
斯坦见鬼去吧
斯坦臭混蛋  甜心奶奶留  派恩斯看好了
你罪有应得  你罪有应得
That's what you get. That's what you get!
我不明白
I don't understand.
我这是招谁惹谁了啊
I completely don't deserve this.
天呐  这个烂摊子得由我们打扫干净吗
Oh, man, are we gonna have to help clean this up?
不  苏斯肯定会搞好这一切的
Nah, I'm sure Soos will take care of it.
话说苏斯哪儿去了
Where is Soos anyway?
好吧  苏斯  记得你奶奶是怎么教你的
Okay, Soos, remember what your grandma taught you.
如果迷路了  你就呆在原地
When you get lost, stay exactly where you are,
不要动
and don't move.
谢谢观看！
不要动
Don't move.
看看  我当稻草人相当不赖呢
You know, I would make a really good scarecrow.